validclick.com 2005-06-29

# ValidClick : About Us

PRIVACY POLICY 

This statement discloses the privacy practices for ValidClick, Inc. and the FeedPatrol product. Our goal is to provide real-time automated fraud-detection technology and search feed management for industry leading paid search providers. 

What Personally Identifiable Information of yours is collected:

When you visit [ValidClick.com](http://validclick.com/) or [FeedPatrol.com](http://feedpatrol.com/), you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself (e.g., contact and demographic information). We use this information to respond to your inquiry about our company or products. 

When you visit a third party website that utilizes a FeedPatrol protected search feed, we will monitor your click activity on that site and collect click activity information, as well as your computer's IP address.

COOKIES 

To enable many of the features available at ValidClick, we may assign "cookies" to your Internet browser. A cookie is a small text file that contains a unique identification number stored on your computer. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. This unique identification number automatically identifies your browser - but not you - to our computers whenever you interact with ValidClick or client site. Only when you agree to provide personally identifiable information to ValidClick or a ValidClick client will we be able to know anything about you other than the random number that our server computers originally assign to your browser. 

ValidClick uses "cookie" technology to make your visits more convenient for you. We use cookies to give you the option of saving shopping cart and contact information so you don't have to enter it repeatedly when you are navigating through a ValidClick client site. These are set so we may better customize your experience on ValidClick for your future visits. You are free to reject or "Not Accept" the placement of some or all of our cookies. 

There is a lot of confusion about cookies, how they are used, and what they can do. Cookies only contain information that the server computer "knew" in the first place, and can only be read by the serving domain that placed them. For instance, if [XYZ.com](http://xyz.com/) (a fictitious company) utilizes cookies, ValidClick's servers can't read their contents nor can [XYZ.com](http://xyz.com/)'s servers read ours. Cookies are an essential part of how the Internet works today, and allow server computers to recognize your computer's browser when you return. If you have ever visited a Web page that automatically provides personalized content without you having to "sign in," such as your own stock portfolio, this is almost certainly being accomplished with a cookie. Since cookies are only text files, they cannot "run" on your computer and have no ability to search your computer for other information, or transmit it to anyone. 

What Organization is collecting the information: 

The data you provide to ValidClick or a ValidClick client site is collected by ValidClick, Inc. 

How the information is used: 

The personal profile information you submit to ValidClick remains your property, but by submitting that information you grant ValidClick the right to use that information for marketing purposes. ValidClick may also use such information to fulfill orders and feedback purposes. 

How the information is shared:

We DO NOT share, rent or sell the personal information that you supply to us, other than with the owners and operators of the ValidClick client website(s) where you submitted such information. We may join together with other businesses to bring selected targeted opportunities to you based on abandoned shopping cart and contact information you submitted. In addition, ValidClick reserves the right to release information collected (1) in the event ValidClick believes such information pertains to an unlawful act, (2) if the information is subpoenaed, (3) if ValidClick is sold or acquired, (4) or when ValidClick deems it necessary or appropriate. 

ValidClick operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our members. 

Third-Party Links 

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other Web sites. We encourage you to note when you are on a third party website utilizing a FeedPatrol protected search feed, you should read the privacy statements of these other Web sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by ValidClick. 

Children

You must be at least 13 years of age to submit information to ValidClick. If you are under 13, you will not be allowed to submit information to ValidClick. ValidClick has implemented this policy and technology to comply with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). 

Contacting ValidClick, Inc. 

ValidClick respects your privacy and uses the information you provide us with integrity and full disclosure. If you ever feel this policy has been broken, let us know. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of ValidClick, or your dealings with us, please contact us by email to Privacy@ [ValidClick.com](http://validclick.com/) or by postal mail to: ValidClick, Inc., 4149 Pennsylvania, Suite 301, Kansas City, MO 64111, Attn: Privacy Dept.
